<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Forex Fourier Analyzer</string>
    <string name="text_welcome">WELCOME TO\nForex Fourier Analyzer</string>
    <string name="text_start">get started</string>

    <string-array name="big_menu">
        <item>Configure Fourier parameters</item>
        <item>Configure currency chart</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tf_items">
        <item>M1</item>
        <item>M5</item>
        <item>M15</item>
        <item>M30</item>
        <item>H1</item>
        <item>H4</item>
        <item>D1</item>
        <item>W1</item>
        <item>MN</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pair_items">
        <item>EURUSD</item>
        <item>GBPUSD</item>
        <item>USDCHF</item>
        <item>USDJPY</item>
        <item>USDCAD</item>
        <item>AUDUSD</item>
        <item>NZDUSD</item>
        <item>AUDCAD</item>
        <item>AUDCHF</item>
        <item>AUDJPY</item>
        <item>AUDNZD</item>
        <item>CADCHF</item>
        <item>CADJPY</item>
        <item>CHFJPY</item>
        <item>EURAUD</item>
        <item>EURCAD</item>
        <item>EURCHF</item>
        <item>EURGBP</item>
        <item>EURJPY</item>
        <item>EURNZD</item>
        <item>GBPAUD</item>
        <item>GBPCAD</item>
        <item>GBPCHF</item>
        <item>GBPJPY</item>
        <item>GBPNZD</item>
        <item>NZDCAD</item>
        <item>NZDCHF</item>
        <item>NZDJPY</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="parameter_bars_in_history">Bars in history</string>

    <string name="parameter_number_of_modes">Number of modes</string>
    <string name="parameter_number_of_harmonics">Number of harmonics</string>
    <string name="parameter_period_of_approximation">Period of approximation</string>
    <string name="parameter_predicted_bars">Predicted bars</string>
    <string name="parameter_min_periods">Minimum periods</string>
    <string name="parameter_max_periods">Maximum periods</string>
    <string name="parameter_period_step">Period step</string>
    <string name="parameter_amplitude_steps">Amplitude steps</string>
    <string name="parameter_phase_step">Phase step</string>
    <string name="parameter_high_freq_filter">High frequency filter</string>
    <string name="parameter_dynamic_approximation">Dynamic approximation</string>

    <string name="number_of_modes_help_text">The number of modes used for approximation.
        Modes divides the period of approximation in segments. Every mode may consist of several harmonics.
        Harmonic expansion of the whole given section of the chart is carried out in the first mode.
        Then the period of harmonic of the highest frequency in the first mode is chosen as the approximation length for the next mode etc.
        We seek harmonics of low frequency at long periods and harmonics of high frequency at short periods this way.\n
        An example:\nImaging the approximation of section of chart having length of 1000 bars by 2 modes of 3 harmonics each.
        First of all the indicator finds 3 harmonics in such a way that its sum approximate the given section of chart in the best way.
        Suppose they are harmonics with period of 600, 450 and 320 bars.
        Then the indicator will try to approximate better the section of chart with length of 320 bars by adding of 3 harmonics to the first mode.
        A curve being a sum of all modes will be plotted in the extrapolated region.</string>

    <string name="number_of_harmonics_help_text">Approximating function is a linear sum of harmonics – sines with different period, amplitude and
phase. The more harmonics the more precisely approximation.</string>

    <string name="period_of_approximation_help_text">The prediction of price moving in future
is based on the approximated segment of the chart.</string>

    <string name="predicted_bars_help_text">The length of extrapolation of the approximated segment of the chart in future.
    The extrapolated curve is painted into two colors. The orange color corresponds to the segment equals to the minimal period among all harmonics used for approximation.
    This segment should be considered as reliable prediction. The rest of the curve is painted into yellow.</string>

    <string name="min_periods_help_text">The minimal number of periods packed in each harmonic. One period corresponds to sine changes from 0 to 2pi.</string>

    <string name="max_periods_help_text">The maximal number of periods packed in each harmonic. One period corresponds to sine changes from 0 to 2pi.</string>

    <string name="period_step_help_text">The period step preset the precision of adjustment of period for each harmonic used for approximation.
    This parameter determines the step of period in bars for the first mode. Step of period for next modes is proportional to their length.
    The resulting number of period steps can be estimated through dividing the period of approximation by the period step.</string>

    <string name="amplitude_steps_help_text">The number of steps for calculation of amplitude of harmonics. The range of searching is determined automatically.</string>

    <string name="phase_step_help_text">The phase step preset the precision of adjustment of phase for each harmonic used for approximation.
    The resulting number of phase steps can be estimated through dividing 2pi by the phase step.</string>

    <string name="high_freq_filter_help_text">The high frequency filter determines the minimal admissible period of a harmonic.
    The period of harmonics can becomes too small during calculation because of the "modes" approach.
    This parameter limits it to avoid oscillations having very high frequency.</string>

    <string name="dynamic_approximation_help_text">Dynamic approximation allows one to consider the nearest past in a greater degree during calculation of harmonics.
        It partly substitute dividing of approximated section on modes. That is to say last oscillations of the price contribute more even at the one-mode regime.</string>

</resources>